hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips this time
这次的 spring 技巧 分期付款
we're going to revisit the Kotlin
我们将重温Kotlin
programming language in the earlier
较早的编程语言
video we looked at a call and and its
我们看了一个电话的视频及其
basic nascent integration with spring
与Spring基本新生
community in the ecosystem and I just
生态系统中的社区，我只是
want to revisit it because a lot of
想重新访问它，因为很多
progress has been made and I want to
已经取得进展，我想
start today with there is simple
从今天开始，很简单
bread-and-butter spring application and
牛油Spring 的应用和
then progress towards a more Kotlin
然后朝着更加Kotlin前进
native sort of approach to building
原生的构建方法
spring application so I'm gonna start
春季申请，所以我要开始
with a bread-and-butter basic JBC sort
基本的JBC排序
of web application here I'm gonna use h2
我将使用H2的Web应用程序
which is an in-memory embedded database
这是一个内存嵌入式数据库
we use the JDBC support we use spring
我们使用JDBC支持我们使用spring
the web support and we're going to use
网络支持，我们将使用
common naturally and spring boot 2005 so
常见的自然和 spring boot 2005
when I hit generate then I'll give us a
当我点击“生成”时，我会给我们一个
new project now I'm gonna open up this
新项目，我要打开这个
application here in my IDE and it
我的IDE中的应用程序
doesn't really matter what I do you're
我做什么都不重要
using of course but it's in treating
当然使用，但这是在治疗
common ontology is a pretty good choice
通用本体是一个不错的选择
now I've got a new bread-and-butter
现在我有了一个新的面包和黄油
application so the first thing I'm going
应用程序，所以我要做的第一件事
to do this I know you know manage my
为此，我知道您知道管理我的
data and I'm gonna do that using the
数据，我将使用
dependencies that on the classpath right
对classpath的依赖
I've got my age to support I've got my
我有我的年龄来支持我有我的
JDBC support I've also got the cotton
JDBC支持我也有能力
standard library and the reflects
标准库和反映
support there I've got the origins
支持那里，我有来历
cotton maven plugin and I've got a
Cotton Maven插件，我有一个
compiler plugin in the maven plug-in
Maven插件中的编译器插件
itself and the compiler plug-in is for
本身和编译器插件用于
spring you see we we have a need in
Spring ，您会看到我们有需要
spring to be able to extend your classes
Spring 来扩展您的课程
to subclass them think about the way
让他们思考方式
most of this stuff is supported right
这些东西大部分都受支持了
spring provides proxies that then extend
Spring 提供了代理，然后扩展
your classes ultimately at runtime you
您的类最终在运行时
you take advantage of the fact of you
你利用了你的事实
take advantage of the the nature of the
利用的性质
Liskov substitution principle I can
我可以的李斯科夫替代原理
substitute any objects of type a for a
用a类型的任何对象代替a
subclass of a right that's the benefit
权利的子类即收益
of that and that's the basis of
这就是那的基础
dependency injection I can describe my
我可以描述依赖注入
code in terms of types that I need and
根据我需要的类型进行编码
as long as I get that type or something
只要我得到那种类型的东西
that specializes that type it'll look so
专门针对这种类型，它将看起来如此
I can swap out or at least subclass
我可以换掉或者至少换一个子类
particular types and then provide that
特定类型，然后提供
reference instead and I get enhanced
相反，我得到了增强
behavior without having to change my
无需更改我的行为
code that depends on that type so that
取决于该类型的代码
works because we can extend your classes
有效，因为我们可以扩展您的课程
in Kotlin by default you have to specify
默认情况下，在Kotlin中，您必须指定
open for class to be subclass of all by
开放给所有类的子类
default if you if you leave this as is
如果您保留原样，则默认
its equivalent to saying final final
相当于说最终
class GBC application in Java and so
Java中的GBC类应用程序等等
we're in Java you have to opt in to
我们在Java中，您必须选择加入
locking down your classes in Kotlin you
在Kotlin锁定课程
have to opt out so what you want to be
必须选择退出，所以你想成为
able to make that as easy as possible
能够使它尽可能容易
since spring requires you topped out for
因为 Spring 需要你顶
all the components that work with spring
与Spring 配合使用的所有组件
so that's what this caught in maven all
所以这就是所有陷入Maven的原因
open plugin does it says whenever you
打开插件会说你什么时候
see a spring annotation like add
看到像添加的Spring 注释
component or at configuration an
组件或配置
annotation that is used to describe that
用于描述的注释
this is a component of spring will
这是 Spring 的一部分
manage
管理
whenever they whenever that condition is
每当他们只要这种情况
met then the class is left open by
见面，然后上课
default that's what this plug-in does
默认是这个插件的作用
along with the compiler plugin so we
以及编译器插件，所以我们
have this here now we can build a new
现在有了这个，我们可以建立一个新的
application we're gonna build an
我们将要构建的应用程序
application that manages data so of
这样管理数据的应用程序
course we'll create a data class called
当然，我们将创建一个名为
customer whose
谁的客户
var var name will
var var name will
string and the VAR ID will be no
字符串，VAR ID将为no
knowable long so I'm gonna have two
知道很久，所以我要两个
fields here maybe this will be null Val
此处的字段可能为空Val
that it's read-only not writable once
它是只读的，一次不能写
you've constructed it and this is these
你已经建造好了，这就是这些
are the constructor this is the
是构造函数，这是
constructor prototype of course and this
当然，构造函数原型
creates a mutable you know read and
创建一个您知道已读的可变项，
write property that is malleable that's
写出具有延展性的财产
what the question mark is and that's
问号是什么，那是
what and that default value will be null
什么以及该默认值将为null
so that's what the equals null means so
这就是等于null的意思
you get a lot of bang for your buck in
你会为此付出很多
this look at this I mean we've got a
看看这个，我的意思是我们有一个
whole object with getters and setters
带有吸气剂和吸气剂的整个对象
and equals and hashcode and constructor
和等于和哈希码和构造函数
and we've already specified whether
并且我们已经指定了
things are read and readable or writable
事物是可读且可读或可写的
we can do all sorts of stuff just for
我们可以做各种各样的事情
that little basic definition and that's
那基本的定义，那就是
good so we can use that now to talk to
好，所以我们现在可以使用它来与
the database so let's create a service
数据库，所以让我们创建一个服务
but actually in our talk today in our
但实际上我们今天在我们的谈话中
time to get together today we're going
今天聚会的时间，我们要去
to look at two different services that
看两个不同的服务
it provides the same interface or as
它提供相同的接口或
implement the same interface so we're
实现相同的接口，所以我们
going to do that we're gonna actually
要做到这一点，我们实际上
provide or define an interface the first
首先提供或定义一个接口
method is going to return all of the
方法将返回所有
records so if collection of all customer
记录是否收集所有客户
and the second one will say by ID ID
第二个将通过ID ID说
long customer question mark so we're
长期的客户问号，所以我们
gonna say find a record by its ID if it
会说通过ID查找记录
exists it might not exist and if it
存在，可能不存在，如果存在
doesn't exist return null if it does
不存在，如果存在则返回null
exist return the actual thing and I'm
存在返回实际的东西，我是
gonna have another method to insert
将有另一种插入方法
objects of type customer into the
客户类型的对象进入
database so we have a customer service
数据库，所以我们有客户服务
interface let's provide our first
界面，让我们提供第一个
implementation and this one will be
实施，这将是
based on the JDBC template customer
基于JDBC模板的客户
service type right so I'm gonna say
服务类型正确，所以我要说
private foul JDBC template and when
私人犯规JDBC模板以及何时
implement the customer service contract
执行客户服务合同
okay and let's see here we are we have
好吧，让我们看看这里，我们有
to override these methods at service at
在服务时覆盖这些方法
transactional
交易性的
and we have to return all the records so
我们必须返回所有记录，以便
this but JBC template.dot query select
这，但JBC template.dot查询选择
all from customers and we need to
全部来自客户，我们需要
provide a road map er the standard
提供路线图标准
signature for this dictates that we need
签名表明我们需要
a some sort of functional interface as
某种功能接口
the last parameter and this works very
最后一个参数，这非常有效
nicely with what we're trying to do in
与我们正在尝试做的很好
lembeh in in common rather you see if we
lembeh的共同点，而是你看看我们
need a lambda as the last argument we
需要一个lambda作为最后一个参数
can specify that outside the invocation
可以指定在调用之外
here so this is the clothes you know
这就是你知道的衣服
right here is the end of the invocation
就在这里是调用的结尾
here I'm starting this this strange
在这里，我开始这个奇怪的事情
block but this is actually a lambda and
块，但这实际上是一个lambda，
it's a lambda of type of rule mapper
这是规则映射器类型的lambda
it's gonna implement the same contract
它将执行相同的合同
and so I'll say that I'm going to map
所以我会说我要去地图
the result set which is this and the
结果集是这个和
offset which is an integer into the
offset是整数
result set I'm gonna map that to a
结果集，我将其映射到
customer object by you know unpacking
客户对象，您知道要拆箱
some values from the results in all
所有结果中的一些值
right that's the that's fairly
对的那是相当的
straightforward right then not so bad
直截了当，然后还不错
let's try this with the the one that has
让我们尝试一下
a predicate more slightly more involved
谓词的参与程度略高
here so equals and here we're gonna look
在这里等于，在这里我们要看
for a specific record and we cannot just
对于特定的记录，我们不能只是
say we need one we need to specify which
说我们需要一个，我们需要指定
one right so we need to provide a
一种权利，所以我们需要提供一个
parameter here so I'm going to pass in
参数在这里，所以我要传递
this ID and of course this doesn't
这个ID，当然这不是
compile I have to tell them that you saw
编译我必须告诉他们你看到了
that a suggestion IntelliJ is saying we
IntelliJ的建议说我们
have an option for you because by
有一个选择给你，因为
default if you look at the query for
如果您查看查询的默认值
object method that the GL person
GL人员的对象方法
supports it gives you a string a row
支持它给你一行字符串
mapper and then a very attic array of
映射器，然后是一个非常阁楼的数组
arguments well I don't want to provide
我不想提供论点
the arguments last otherwise I'll lose
争论不休，否则我会输
out on the convenience where I can
在我可以方便的地方
provide the lambda as the last argument
提供lambda作为最后一个参数
and have that written outside of the
并将其写在
invocation so instead I want the
调用，所以我想要
arguments to come first and then I want
首先要论证，然后我要
the row mapper so we have it a call an
行映射器，所以我们称之为
extension here that does just that it
扩展在这里做到了
says query for object equals string
说查询对象等于字符串
verdict array of arguments in carlin and
在carlin和
then a lambda definition this is this
那么lambda定义就是这个
says I care about a result set and an
说我在乎结果集和
integer and I'm gonna return a T it
整数，我要返回T
doesn't say I need a row mapper all
并没有说我需要一个行映射器
right we don't have to do a function
对，我们不必做一个功能
interface here we just provide an actual
界面，我们只是提供一个实际的
honest-to-goodness lambda right and then
诚实至善的Lambda，然后
that gets mapped into query object
映射到查询对象
taking a row mapper
以行映射器
you know overwriting the result set
你知道覆盖结果集
blah blah blah blah okay so we we get
等等等等等等，所以我们
that for free that's a call an extension
是免费的，这是附加电话信息
in Spring Framework five right you can
在Spring Framework中，五个您可以
see that was on the class but already
看到那是在课堂上，但已经
it's on Spring Framework or extreme form
它在Spring Framework或极端形式上
of GBC core if using Java you'll never
如果使用Java，GBC核心将永远不会
see it you'll never know about it you
看到它，你永远不会知道它，你
don't care but if yours in Kotlin that
不在乎，但如果您在Kotlin那
code will work for you right all right
代码会为您工作
so last one customer we have to insert
所以最后一位客户我们必须插入
some data so we'll say this stuff
一些数据，所以我们会说这些东西
Jaime's template that executes insert
Jaime执行插入的模板
into customers name values question mark
进入客户名称值问号
and here to may is a lambda and the
而这里可能是lambda和
defaults the the the lambda is gonna be
默认为lambda将是
a prepared statement I could specify
我可以指定一份准备好的陈述
that if I want to but I can also do fly
如果我想，但我也可以飞
on caught them to give me an implicit
抓住他们给我一个隐含的
parameter it it is the prepared
它是准备好的参数
statement sorry it thought set string
声明对不起，以为设置了字符串
one is going to be equal to customer dot
一个将等于客户点
name and it not execute there we are
名称，它不执行，我们在
so I've overridden the the insert method
所以我重写了insert方法
there I provide the definition and I'm
在那里，我提供了定义，我是
using the JDBC template to write data to
使用JDBC模板将数据写入
the database the question of course then
数据库当然是问题
is what database what schema a table so
什么数据库是什么架构表
we can take advantage of a mechanism
我们可以利用一种机制
here and spring itself not not even
这里和 Spring 本身甚至没有
spring butjust spring I can say schema
我可以说架构
that's equal and if I say insert into
那是相等的，如果我说插入
customer so I'm sorry I want to create
客户，对不起，我想创建
the table and say create table customers
表并说创建表客户
and I'm gonna provide a semicolon
我要提供一个分号
the only semicolon you're gonna see me
你唯一要见我的分号
type this for this installation that's
为此安装输入
gonna have an ID big int auto increment
将会有一个ID big int自动递增
primary key and a name var car two five
主键和一个名称var car两个5
five not null all right so there's my
五个不为零，好吧，那是我的
scheme on my DDL and springs gonna run
DDL上的方案和Spring 将运行
that when the application starts up and
当应用程序启动时
this is gonna work so now let's go ahead
这将起作用，所以现在让我们继续
and exercise it will created an
并锻炼它会创建一个
implementation we're creating an object
实现我们正在创建一个对象
that actually exercises the service and
实际上行使服务
it's gonna get an application winner so
它将会获得应用程序的赢家，所以
I could do what I normally do right I
我可以做我通常会做的事
can just say you know data initializer
只能说你知道数据初始化器
and override the application runner and
并覆盖应用程序运行程序和
inject this here private Val customer
在这里注入此私人Val客户
service and make this a regular spin
服务，并使其定期旋转
component and all of that is fine I mean
组件，所有这些都很好，我的意思是
that would certainly work but there's
那肯定会工作，但是有
actually a much more Colin esque
实际上是科林式的
approach right we can use
我们可以使用的正确方法
functional beam registration right so
功能光束配准正确
instead of using Java config or
而不是使用Java config或
component scanning here we say spring
组件扫描在这里，我们说 Spring
application builder dot initializers
应用程序构建器点初始化器
beans provide that beans definition and
bean提供了bean的定义和
we'll come back to that a second that's
我们将回到那一秒钟
like the DSL that we want to use when
就像我们想在什么时候使用的DSL
I'll specify which class to use in this
我将在此指定要使用的类
case GV application class Java and we
案例GV应用程序类Java，我们
can tell it to run passing in the
可以告诉它运行通过
arguments so this is the list of
参数，所以这是
arguments at want to provide and the DSL
要提供的参数和DSL
let's just define means using this very
让我们只定义使用这个方法
nice DSL that that will get run with the
不错的DSL，它将与
registered application context right now
现在注册的应用程序上下文
there isn't it there's an analog to this
不，有一个类似的东西
there's function you can do functional
有功能可以做功能
mean definitions in Java as well but
也意味着Java中的定义，但
this call in DSL was unique to common
DSL中的此呼叫是常见的
right it and I think it reads much more
正确，我认为它读得更多
nicely so here we're gonna create a beam
很好，所以在这里我们要创建一个光束
of type application runner and in the
类型的应用程序运行程序和
application runner we need a pointer to
应用程序运行程序，我们需要一个指向
the customer service so normally we'd
客户服务，所以通常我们会
ask spring to inject us in a bean
要求 Spring 给我们注入 Bean type
provider method here we say give me a
提供者方法在这里，我们说给我一个
reference to it and you do that by
引用它，您可以通过
asking for this ref by calling the ref
通过致电裁判索取该裁判
method this ref method it doesn't need a
方法此ref方法不需要
class literal right well remember
类字面量正确，请记住
ultimately what it's going to do is is
最终要做的是
gonna go to the application context and
转到应用程序上下文并
say give me a bean of this type well
说好好给我这种 bean
that type is only you know we don't have
这种类型只是你知道我们没有
a class little hair but complet has this
一类小毛发，但完整
nice feature work and ray of phi generic
不错的功能和phi phi泛型
signatures are generic information for
签名是关于
inline methods so if you look at this it
内联方法，所以如果你看这个
says inline fun ray if I'd T and then it
说，如果我愿意，那么内联趣味雷
returns T so this this has the effect of
返回T，所以这具有
basically capturing the generic type
基本捕获通用类型
signature here and making it said I can
在这里签名并说我可以
talk about it as a class literal TD I
将此作为类文字TD I谈论
can t class Java right now I'm actually
我现在不能上Java
able to say T that get class basically
能够说基本的T
and this is possible because when it
这是可能的，因为当它
says inlined
内联说
what it means is that this function has
这意味着该功能具有
been copied and pasted into the call
复制并粘贴到通话中
site it's a macro if you will you're
网站，如果您愿意，这是一个宏
there's no stack it's actually just
没有堆栈，实际上只是
copying and pasting that code and at the
复制并粘贴该代码，并在
place where you're calling it and it's
你打电话的地方，它是
able to capture the argument as you have
能够按需捕获论点
it right then and there because Minoo
那是因为美浓
you're not passing around it's just
你没有绕过它，只是
braid that in there right it can capture
编织在那里可以捕捉
that and keeps it on an implicit
并将其保留在隐式
variable that's you know
你知道的变量
from your code you have to worry about
从您的代码中，您不必担心
it it's not true reification but for our
这不是真正的修正，而是为了我们
purposes it works right this is this
目的是正确的，这是这个
this ref method at runtime or have a
此ref方法在运行时或具有
pointer to the type that you've used
指向您使用过的类型的指针
here
这里
and then we can use that to write some
然后我们可以用它来写一些
data to the database so let's do that
数据存储到数据库中，所以让我们这样做
array of let's see Tammy Mario Andrew
让我们来看看Tammy Mario Andrew
and Cornelia there we are okay so
和科妮莉亚，我们还好，所以
there's that and I'm going to visit each
就是这样，我要去参观每个
one I'm going to map each one I suppose
我要映射每个我想的一个
so we'll say map each one to a customer
所以我们说将每个人映射到一个客户
whose name is equal to it and then win
其名字等于它然后赢
us for each one of those will say that
我们对于每个人都会说
the name a so we'll say customer service
名字a，所以我们说客户服务
dot insert it alright so there's our
点插入好吧，这是我们的
records and I want to say customer
记录，我想说客户
service dot all done for each and print
每个服务点都已完成并打印
out the results here we are ok so I
出来的结果在这里我们还可以，所以我
would run that let's see what we get
将运行，让我们看看我们得到了什么
you can see the compiler is telling us
您可以看到编译器告诉我们
in a few cases where these AI arguments
在某些情况下，这些AI参数
are never used and it could be renamed
从未使用过，可以重命名
to just underscore to signify that
只是强调表示
though we need to satisfy that parameter
尽管我们需要满足该参数
for the the constructor for the
为的构造函数
interface they're useless we don't need
界面，它们是无用的，我们不需要
them don't worry about them don't don't
他们不用担心他们不要不要
waste cognitive effort cognitive effort
浪费认知努力认知努力
trying to feel what they do all right so
试图感觉他们所做的一切都很好
there's the results on the database on
在数据库上有结果
the console that seems to work seems to
似乎正常工作的控制台似乎
have worked and you know that's not
已经工作了，你知道那不是
surprising this is a very simple code
令人惊讶的是，这是一个非常简单的代码
and we can pretty easily sort of guess
我们可以很容易地猜测
that what the queries are gonna be if we
如果我们要查询什么
had something more sophisticated we
有一些更复杂的东西
might want to do something that makes
可能想做一些使
getting the right result easier type
获得正确结果更容易键入
safety can be very valuable here and so
安全在这里可能非常有价值
we can use a third-party library a
我们可以使用第三方库
common library from JetBrains The
JetBrains的公共库
Pretenders of Colin called exposed it's
冒充科林的伪装者称其为
a norm framework that also works very
一个非常有效的规范框架
nicely with spring so let's do that
很好地与 Spring ，所以让我们做到这一点
instead
代替
well use exposed and I'll copy and paste
好用暴露，我将复制并粘贴
this and we use a spring transaction and
这，我们使用春季交易，
exposed needs a well first let's comment
暴露需要一个很好的让我们先评论
this out and exposed in order to do its
这个出来并暴露出来，以做到其
work it needs schema we've already got a
工作它需要模式，我们已经有一个
schema file but let's rename this to be
模式文件，但让我们将其重命名为
schema.org okay and then in the schema
schema.org好的，然后在架构中
definition or for us to provide the
定义或由我们提供
schema definition we have to provide an
模式定义，我们必须提供
object customers that extends table now
现在扩展表的对象客户
this syntax in in in Kotlin it's very
在Kotlin中的这种语法非常
hard to have static fields or methods in
很难有静态字段或方法
a class you have to create a separate
一个类，您必须创建一个单独的类
object a singleton object and you can
反对一个单身的对象，你可以
store things in there so this is
在那里存储东西，所以这是
separate this is a separate construct in
独立的，这是一个独立的结构
a class it's a single class that has
一个类，它是一个具有
functions that live in a single
单一功能
namespace two thing like static methods
命名空间两件事就像静态方法
in Java and here we're gonna define our
在Java中，在这里我们将定义我们的
detail if we're gonna say that there's
细节，如果我们要说有
gonna be a field called ID that is a
将是一个称为ID的字段
long field called ID it's gonna be auto
长字段称为ID，它将是自动的
incrementing and it'll be the primary
递增，它将是主要的
key we're gonna have a named field it's
关键是我们要有一个命名字段
gonna be var car name and that's it
将会是var的汽车名称，仅此而已
that's our definition that's our DDL now
那就是我们的定义那就是我们的DDL
I want to create an exposed customer
我想创建一个暴露的客户
service
服务
and it's going to implement the customer
这将实现客户
service contract all right
服务合同没事
there's this very good okay now this is
这很好，现在是
a spring beam as before and it's gonna
像以前一样的Spring 梁
be ad transactional as before and in
像以前和之前一样进行广告交易
order for us to create that DDL we need
为了让我们创建该DDL，我们需要
to have a life cycle call back we're
有一个生命周期回电，我们
gonna tell spring to call this an it
要告诉 Spring 叫这个
method when the application starts up in
应用程序启动时的方法
there and we're gonna call schema util
在那里，我们将调用架构实用程序
dot create customers this has to happen
点创建客户这必须发生
within a transactional boundary so even
在交易范围内
though we've got add transactional the
尽管我们添加了交易性的
content of this method that what happens
这种方法的内容发生了什么
in here isn't gonna be transactional by
在这里不会被交易
default that happens after this method
此方法之后发生的默认设置
is called so we need to wrap this in a
被称为，所以我们需要将其包装在
transactional boundary and what I'm
交易边界和我是什么
gonna do that is to use a private val
要做的就是使用私有val
transaction template alright a
交易模板还可以
transaction template from spring is a
Spring 的交易模板是
object spinning spring for more than a
物体旋转Spring 不止一个
decade it's a wrapper around the
十年，这是一个包装
platform content and transaction manager
平台内容和交易管理器
abstraction and for our purposes allows
为了我们的目的，抽象允许
us to say that we want to run this code
我们说我们想运行这段代码
in a transactional boundary now the
在交易边界中
execute method itself oops the execute
execute方法本身会执行
method itself takes a transaction
方法本身需要进行交易
callback which of course as a functional
回调当然是功能
interface which has one method of type
具有一种类型方法的接口
doing transaction which takes a single
做一次交易
parameter in this case we can rely upon
在这种情况下，我们可以依靠
the implicit parameter it
隐式参数
that's the transaction status so we
这就是交易状态，所以我们
don't need it or we can declare it and
不需要它，我们可以声明它，并且
we could say TS equals whatever but
我们可以说TS等于
either way we're just gonna run this one
无论哪种方式，我们都将运行这个
little bit of code in a custom
自定义中的少量代码
transactional block the rest of these
事务性阻止其余的这些
will be managed for us automatically
将自动为我们管理
ok so let's implement our service in
好的，让我们在以下方面实施我们的服务
terms of this new integration so select
此新集成的条款，请选择
all and I'm going to map the results
全部，我将映射结果
going to say give me a customer back
要说给我回顾客
where I map the IT customers dot name
我在哪里映射IT客户点名称
and the IT customers dot ID and that's
IT客户的点号是
my omit that's it it's a type safe DSL
我的遗漏是它是类型安全的DSL
right I don't have to I don't have to do
对，我不必做
anything more than that I'm going to do
除了我要做的以外
the same thing here so customers dot
同样的事情在这里让客户点
select and here I need to provide a
选择，在这里我需要提供一个
predicate I need to say customers that
谓语我需要说客户
ID that equals
等于的ID
Eydie right let's took predicated coming
艾迪（Eydie）对，让我们预言未来的到来
for the method and then we say map and
方法，然后我们说map和
I'll just reuse this definition up here
我将在这里重用此定义
okay and we're gonna say first or Knoll
好吧，我们先说还是诺尔
so we're gonna create a mapping what a
所以我们要创建一个映射
map we're gonna say select all turn them
地图，我们要说全选
into objects and then give me the first
进入物体，然后先给我
one or no that's why we have this
一个或没有，这就是为什么我们有这个
question mark there and then finally for
问号在那里，然后终于
the insert it's a also very strict for
插入它也非常严格
we say customers dot insert and we're
我们说客户点插入，我们
gonna say it's that customers that ID
要说的是客户的ID
our name rather equals customer dot name
我们的名字等于客户点的名字
right so there we go we have everything
对，所以我们走了，我们拥有了一切
we need to be able to use that out of
我们需要能够使用它
the box that is a very very simple type
一个非常简单的盒子
safety SL but you can do very complex
安全SL，但您可以做的很复杂
things very very powerful complex things
事物非常非常强大，复杂的事物
like joins and so on all on this type
像联接等等，都是这种类型的
safety SL you don't ever have to drop
安全SL，您无需掉落
down to extremely sequel and indeed even
甚至极度续集，甚至
the definition of the of the DDL itself
DDL本身的定义
is done for you
为您完成
using this type safe DSL so let's now
使用这种类型的安全DSL，现在让我们
rerun this code I've commented out the
重新运行此代码，我已经注释掉了
JDBC implementation but as we are
JDBC实现
implementing the customer service
实施客户服务
contract for this our initializer which
为此我们的初始化程序的合同
depends on that customer service will
取决于客户服务将
still work let's run that oh I need to
仍在工作，让我们运行哦，我需要
specify the length and the compiler
指定长度和编译器
thought that for me
以为我
now exposed requires joda-time
现在暴露需要乔达时间
and it also requires integration sorry
而且还需要集成抱歉
it requires it doesn't record to the
它要求它不记录到
time it requires integration with our
需要与我们整合的时间
transaction management mechanism this
交易管理机制
come this error here is saying please
来这里这个错误是说请
call Davies start connect before running
打电话给Davies在运行之前开始连接
this code and that indicates to me that
此代码，并向我表明
it hasn't actually committed the
它实际上并没有承诺
transaction before so we've actually
之前的交易，所以我们实际上
done but it's looking for we've done
完成，但它正在寻找我们已经完成
this here but this transaction template
这里，但是这个交易模板
doesn't know about our platform
不知道我们的平台
transaction manager the plan checks
交易经理计划检查
transaction template knows about Springs
交易模板了解Springs
platform transaction manager interface
平台交易管理器界面
there are many different implementations
有很多不同的实现
of that interface for different kinds of
该界面针对不同种类的
resources you know from different kinds
您从不同种类了解的资源
of transactions we need to provide the
我们需要提供的交易
exposed one called spring transaction
暴露了一项叫做春季交易的交易
manager and we can do that here and just
经理，我们可以在这里做到
it expects a reference to our data
它希望参考我们的数据
source right we're going to provide that
权利，我们将提供
here it's verified as I said before so
正如我之前所说的，这里已经过验证
you'll get you know this spring
今年 Spring 你会知道的
transaction manager is expecting a data
交易经理期待数据
source and it's gotten that already this
来源，已经知道
is of course a implementation from the
当然是
JetBrains exposed library it in turn
JetBrains依次将库暴露出来
extends Springs own data source
扩展Springs自己的数据源
transaction manager which in turn
交易经理
extends the abstract platform
扩展抽象平台
implements platform transaction manager
实施平台交易管理器
so we can now reuse that implementation
所以我们现在可以重用该实现
here and hopefully it doesn't work let's
在这里，希望它不起作用，让我们
run this code oh it does require
运行此代码哦，确实需要
joda-time
乔达时间
yes so let's bring that in as well I
是的，所以我们也将其引入
don't know why it requires two at a time
不知道为什么一次需要两个
I would love to know why I have to bring
我很想知道为什么我必须带
that in and why it doesn't just do it
那以及为什么它不只是这样做
for me but we'll leave it at this
对我来说，但我们会留在这里
all right very good so there are records
很好很好所以有记录
in the database all four records that's
在数据库中的所有四个记录是
a very simple bread-and-butter kind of
一种非常简单的面包和黄油
application we can build a tres
我们可以建立一个应用程序
controller we could say customer rest
控制器，我们可以说客户休息
controller using spring MVC so and get
控制器使用spring MVC等并获得
mapping customers fun customers equals
为客户映射有趣的客户等于
and we want to inject the private Val
我们想注入私人瓦尔
customer service at risk controller
风险控制人员的客户服务
equals this that customer service dot
等于这个客户服务点
all and run the code again
全部并再次运行代码
localhost:8080
本地主机：8080
customers oh it's blocked Kotlin by
客户哦，它阻止了Kotlin
default the integration intelligent
默认集成智能
common is not smart enough to set single
普通不足以设置单身
instance only so I'm running a spring
仅实例，所以我正在运行Spring
good application it'll collide with the
好的应用程序会与
existing application that's running on
正在运行的现有应用程序
the same port and one of them will fail
同一端口，其中一个将失败
so this one the second one failed here
所以这个第二个在这里失败了
I'm gonna kill that off run the
我要杀掉那个
application again localhost customers
再次应用localhost客户
okay let's see what I choose customer I
好吧，让我们看看我选择的客户我
chose that's the wrong URL but if I had
选择了错误的网址，但是如果我有
specified s as I should have that would
指定s，因为我应该有
have worked as well all right so we have
一切都很好，所以我们有
now a very simple spring application
现在是一个非常简单的spring应用程序
using bread and butter technologies
使用面包和黄油技术
again we're using JDBC and spring MVC
再次，我们使用JDBC和spring MVC
which in turn is based on the servlet
反过来基于servlet
stuff so you know this is very clean
东西，所以你知道这很干净
very automatic very you know modern
非常自动，非常现代
approach and way to work with
的方法和方式
fundamentally decades-old technology
拥有数十年历史的技术
I mean JDBC and servlets are very old
我的意思是JDBC和servlet很老
and they worked just fine they're there
他们很好，他们在那里
you know like I said bread-and-butter
你知道我说的是面包和黄油
kind stuff but while we've gotten some
好东西，但是当我们得到一些
benefit from the cotton extensions in
受益于棉花延伸
traditional spring api's right where i
传统的春季api正确的地方
think there's a lot of really
认为真的有很多
interesting stuff to see than a new api
比新的api有趣的东西
so let's now build a new application
现在让我们构建一个新的应用程序
similar to this one well go back to
与这口井相似，回到
start out spring today oh and we'll use
今天从 Spring 开始哦，我们将使用
the reactive stuff reactive support and
反应性物质反应性支持和
spring webflix which is in turn part of
Spring 的webflix，这反过来又是
Spring Framework 5 so I use spring Mutoh
Spring Framework 5，所以我使用Spring Mutoh
Cottman of course
科特曼当然
I'm going to use reactive web but
我要使用反应式网页
reactive
反应性
MongoDB and we're going to use gateway
MongoDB，我们将使用网关
spring cloud gateway okay a new project
Spring Cloud Gateway好的新项目
for for stand up API gateways so I've
用于站起来的API网关，所以我已经
got that now let's say you AoE active
知道了，假设您的AoE活跃
zip open this up on the IDE
zip在IDE上打开它
all right so we have a new application
好的，所以我们有一个新的应用程序
and same as before we'll create a data
和之前一样，我们将创建一个数据
entity a data a class customer but this
实体数据类客户，但这
one will map to database so using
一个将映射到数据库，所以使用
MongoDB so we the idea will be a strain
MongoDB，所以我们的想法很紧张
question run all of our name string
问题运行我们所有的名称字符串
question mark equals at all it's gonna
问号完全等于
be a document let's bring down a MongoDB
作为文档，让我们关闭一个MongoDB
document and it'll have a primary key
文档，它将有一个主键
whose ID is a 5 ID and that's it that's
其ID为5 ID，仅此而已
the basic definition of our type and
我们类型的基本定义和
we're gonna use the spring data among
我们将使用Spring 数据
going to be a reactive MongoDB
将成为一个反应性的MongoDB
repository support so I'm gonna say
存储库支持，所以我要说
customer service cost reactive Mongo
客户服务成本反应式Mongo
repository managing entities of type
类型的存储库管理实体
customer whose primary key it's a type
主键是类型的客户
string and now we're going to save some
字符串，现在我们要保存一些
data to database so again as we did last
数据再次存储到数据库中
time we're gonna say spring application
时间我们要说春季申请
builder dot initializers beans alt enter
构建器点初始化器bean alt输入
when I say sources is equal to reactive
当我说来源等于反应性
application reactive application class
应用程序反应式应用程序类
Java and I'm going to tell it to run
Java，我要告诉它运行
down here ok
在这里好吗
passing the orgs there we are
通过组织在那里
and the initializers in the beam the
和光束中的初始值设定项
first thing I'm going to do is I'm going
我要做的第一件事就是我要
to write some day-to-day basis as we did
像我们一样每天写一些基础
earlier so customer repository equals
较早，因此客户存储库等于
ref customer repository or customer
ref客户资料库或客户
repository here we are okay
仓库在这里我们还好
could have been customer service
本来可以是客户服务
couldn't have I would have been okay I
不能，我会没事的
guess as well all right there's the ref
猜猜还好吧，那里的裁判
we need to create a beam of course so
我们当然需要创建一个光束
this is could be inside that mean
这可能是在那个意思里面
definition and we're gonna write some
定义，我们要写一些
data out so we're gonna say save
数据出来，所以我们要说保存
customer ID so our name equals let's see
客户ID，所以我们的名字等于
well actually I want to create some
好吧，我想创建一些
records and save them reactively so
记录并被动地保存它们，以便
let's do this the using another
让我们使用另一个
extension here we're going to use list
扩展这里，我们将使用列表
of you know Margaret mat Michelle
你们知道玛格丽特垫米歇尔
Michael okay so for MS and I want to
迈克尔好吧，对于MS，我想
turn this into a publisher the publisher
变成出版商
of type flux and that's a context it's
类型的通量，这是它的上下文
an extension to Kotlin sequences cotton
Kotlin序列棉的扩展
collections that turns it into a flux
将其变成通量的集合
and that to flux method comes from the
而通量法则来自
reactor core integration for common
反应堆堆芯集成通用
right it's the common extension so cuz
对，这是常见的扩展名，所以
turn it into a publisher a directive
把它变成发布者的指令
steam publisher and then we can visit
Steam发行商，然后我们可以访问
each one of those we're gonna say map
我们要说的每个地图
each one to a customer
每个给客户
those game is equal to that I want to
那些游戏等于我想要的
turn to see this all so I'm gonna see
转过来看这一切，我要去看看
map that and then flat map that by
映射，然后通过
saving it in the database so customer
将其保存在数据库中，以便客户
pause right at save passing in it and
在保存通过时暂停，然后
that'll give us Val customers equals a
这将使我们的Val客户等于
publisher of customer and I'm Eric and
客户的发布者，我是Eric，
we can save the data we can say customer
我们可以保存可以说客户的数据
pause right out delete all but then many
暂停一下，然后删除所有
customers that then many customer posit
那么许多客户提出的客户
or not find all dot subscribe right
还是找不到所有的点订阅权
print mine IT very good so we have now
打印我的IT非常好，所以我们现在有
the list of publishers and the dinner
出版商名单和晚宴
should be written in the database when
应该在什么时候写到数据库中
the application starts up let's confirm
该应用程序启动，让我们确认
as much by running application
通过运行应用程序
all right so that work just fine we got
好的，这样工作就可以了
the four records in the database we've
数据库中的四个记录
got their IDs all that stuff is just
得到他们的身份证，所有的东西只是
working as we expect for your little
像我们期望的那样工作
code so far let's build a REST API so
到目前为止的代码，让我们构建一个REST API，以便
again here we can use a nice new feature
再次在这里我们可以使用一个不错的新功能
in Spring Framework five and spring Webb
在Spring Framework 5和Spring Webb中
flux the reactive web runtime here we
在这里修改反应式Web运行时
can say that we want to define our
可以说我们想定义我们的
endpoints using functional reactive
使用功能性反应的端点
endpoints and again we could use the
端点，我们可以再次使用
spring with MVC style controllers as we
随着我们的MVC样式控制器的出现
did in the last example but this is I
在上一个示例中做了，但这是我
think a little bit more this was gonna
认为这会多一点
be very approachable if you're doing
如果你做的话很平易近人
Kotler and you want to you know least
科特勒，你想知道得最少
amount of code for the results so what
结果的代码量如何
we're gonna do we're to do what we're
我们要去做我们要做的
gonna just want to use it function
只是想使用它的功能
reactive endpoints and we use the Kotlin
反应性终点，我们使用Kotlin
DSL which makes it even more succinct so
DSL使得它更加简洁
mater get customers and our job is to
赢得客户，我们的工作是
return a server response that okay body
返回一个好的服务器响应
and we're going to need the customer
我们将需要客户
repository so customer repository equals
仓库，因此客户仓库等于
rift customer repository and we're gonna
纵容客户资源库，我们将
say customer repository don't find all
说客户存储库找不到全部
it's a return to flux of customers a
这是客户流向的回报
publisher of customers notice that we're
客户发布者注意到我们
being provided an extension that we can
被提供了扩展，我们可以
interact with and we want that extension
与我们互动，我们想要该扩展
because otherwise without that extension
因为否则没有扩展名
we'd have to provide a class literal or
我们必须提供一个类文字或
a super type token you know as
您知道的超级类型令牌
represented by the parameterize type
由参数化类型表示
reference in the spring ecosystem that
在春季生态系统中提到
told the publisher told the web runtime
告诉发布者告诉网络运行时
where to do data framing remember that
在哪里做数据构架请记住
publisher could produce a you know a
发布者可以产生一个您知道的
trillion values it could go on forever
万亿价值，它可能永远持续下去
it could never stop and that's perfectly
它永远不会停止，那是完美的
semantically okay the web runtime needs
Web运行时需要在语义上还可以
to know when to frame the responses
知道何时制定响应
though when to you know it doesn't want
虽然什么时候知道你不想要
to wait into the last byte especially if
等待最后一个字节，特别是如果
that last byte is never gonna arrive so
最后一个字节永远不会到达所以
that publisher needs a clue as to when
该发布者需要有关何时的线索
it should start you know when it should
它应该开始你知道什么时候应该
you know at what point it should take
你知道应该在什么时候
what it's got and then send it back to
它有什么，然后将其发送回
the client and we're gonna say send it
客户，我们要说发送
back for every single customer entity it
为每个客户实体返回
needs to know what that shape what the
需要知道什么形状
shape of that customer is and we do that
该客户的形状是，我们这样做
normally in the Java API by providing
通常在Java API中，通过提供
customer class Java as a class the
客户类Java作为类
reference our class literal but because
引用我们的类文字，但是因为
we have this common extension it's ray
我们有这个共同的扩展名是ray
if I'd right it's already it's captured
如果我正确的话，它已经被捕获了
in line on the site invocation there so
根据网站的调用在那里
now we have this
现在我们有这个
react to the endpoint API that'll work
对将起作用的端点API做出反应
just fine let's go ahead and start this
很好，让我们开始
up now this is you know this is a good
现在这是你知道这是一个好
example of an API whoops I should kill
我应该杀死的API声音示例
the other one otherwise we'll run into
另一个，否则我们会遇到
the same problems this is a good example
同样的问题，这是一个很好的例子
of an API that works just fine you know
您知道的API正常工作
using reactive stuff of course let's say
当然使用反应性材料
this is more than just a service let's
这不仅仅是一项服务，我们
say that this is also an edge service
说这也是一项边缘服务
not just a REST API with an edge service
不只是带有边缘服务的REST API
it's the back end for a front-end or
它是前端的后端，或者
it's the integration with with your with
与您的整合
some other technology
其他一些技术
maybe it's the the thing that is the
也许是那个东西
first port of call for requests coming
请求的第一个呼叫端口
from the outside to the downstream
从外到下游
services whatever it is we want to proxy
提供我们想要代理的服务
some data from one place to another and
一些数据从一个地方到另一个地方
here we could use ool but Zul has a
在这里我们可以使用ool，但是Zul有一个
number of limitations there was a
限制数量有一个
project from Netflix and we integrate
来自Netflix的项目，我们进行了整合
that with with spring cloud we do a lot
与 Spring 的云，我们做了很多
of work to make it powerful but it's not
使其强大的工作，但并非如此
gonna be a great fit for a reactive
非常适合被动式
streams based applications and it also
基于流的应用程序
doesn't support other protocols besides
不支持其他协议
HTTP and also the API is a little clumsy
HTTP和API有点笨拙
if you're dreading filters or if you're
如果您害怕过滤器，或者
trying to integrate its functionality
试图整合其功能
with a spring ecosystem so we have a new
Spring 的生态系统，所以我们有了一个新的
project called spring cloud gateway and
名为Spring Cloud Gateway的项目
spring cloud gateway it's just that it's
Spring Cloud Gateway就是
a gateway technology it builds on Spring
它基于Spring的网关技术
Framework 5 so of course it's the the
框架5当然是
incarnation that we're using is only
我们正在使用的化身只是
available in spring plant Finchley and
在春季工厂Finchley和
we're gonna use the reactive incarnation
我们将使用反应性化身
of that rather the Kotlin extension for
而不是Kotlin扩展
that as well it's gonna help us so we
那也将帮助我们，所以我们
have on a class path spring cloud
在课堂上有Spring Cloud
gateway and we need to bring in the
网关，我们需要引入
Kotlin extensions this is a temporary
Kotlin扩展名，这是临时的
situation right the cotton extensions
正确的棉花延伸情况
will eventually just be in the same
最终将处于同一状态
codebase and you won't have to bring in
代码库，您无需引入
a separate library but for now you know
一个单独的图书馆，但现在您知道了
we do we have to do we have to do that
我们要做我们必须要做的
not a big deal so here's how you
没什么大不了的，所以这就是你
describe the gateway here we're gonna
在这里描述网关
create configurations here using the
使用以下命令在此处创建配置
cotton DSL this very nice DSL we're
棉花DSL这是我们非常好的DSL
gonna say that we want to create a route
要说我们要创建一条路线
that proxies calls to our endpoint to
代理调用我们的端点以
our local node and then routes that to a
我们的本地节点，然后将其路由到
to the blog output the blog feed the RSS
到博客输出博客提要RSS
feed the atom feed rather for our spring
为我们的 Spring 喂原子饲料
IO blog ok so here we are
IO博客好，所以我们在这里
and copy and paste that URL so I'm gonna
然后复制并粘贴该网址，这样我就可以
say if a request comes in that matches
说是否有匹配的请求
path blog when user requests the Gateway
用户请求网关时的路径博客
handler predicates wrapper tickets path
处理程序谓词包装器票证路径
or path Adam and notice that we're using
或走到亚当的路上，注意我们正在使用
this or method here right this is
这是这里的方法
actually an infix function in Kotlin i
实际上是Kotlin中的中缀函数
don't have to provide the method
不必提供方法
parentheses and so it allows I did it
括号，所以它允许我这样做
because it's called an infix function
因为它被称为中缀函数
and the result is I can write these very
结果是我可以写这些
clean sort of DSL right I have this in
干净的DSL，我有这个
flux notation and that's just working
通量表示法，这只是工作
for me now I can say when you match
现在对我来说我可以说你什么时候比赛
something when something matches that
当某物与之匹配时
pattern proxy it to this endpoint I
模式代理它到这个端点我
could by the way use a low bounce URL
可以使用较低的跳出网址
here all right I can actually have a URI
好的，我实际上可以拥有一个URI
that goes to lb that's the load bouncer
达到磅，这是负载弹跳器
fool - service I'll be the load bouncer
傻瓜-服务我将成为负载的保镖
in this case would be something you know
在这种情况下，你会知道
ribbon Netflix ribbon in working in
Netflix功能区工作
conjunction with a discovery kind of
与一种发现相结合
spring cloud discovery client
Spring Cloud 发现客户端
implementation that in turn can talk to
可以与之交谈的实现
things like Apache zookeeper and Netflix
诸如Apache zookeeper和Netflix之类的东西
you week hashey core console etc so I
你一周哈希的核心控制台等，所以我
could do that certainly and I can even
当然可以做到，我什至可以
do other interesting things like there's
做其他有趣的事情，例如
gateway filters that you can provide
您可以提供的网关过滤器
that support things like load balancing
支持诸如负载平衡之类的功能
rate limiting and and circuit breaking
限速和断路
right I can do all that stuff as well
好吧，我也可以做所有的事情
but for our purposes it's probably fine
但出于我们的目的，可能还不错
just to leave this as it is and get rid
只是保持原样并摆脱它
of that and do that and then rerun the
这样做，然后重新运行
application
应用
all right so localhost customers there's
好吧，所以本地客户那里
that let's go to the consult for this
那我们去咨询一下
last look here we're gonna say curl
最后看这里，我们要说卷曲
minus V and get that good and we also
减V并得到那么好，我们也
have this one called the blog look at
有这个叫博客的人看看
the headers that comes back lips head
回到嘴唇头的头
and when we do that we can see that we
当我们这样做时，我们可以看到我们
get these the the RSS feed of course the
得到这些，当然是RSS提要
atom feed rather and we get the content
原子饲料，而我们得到的内容
types and all that stuff that we've
类型以及我们拥有的所有东西
gotten afraid called the service
害怕叫服务
directly so we're actually proxying the
直接，所以我们实际上是代理
results using this highly efficient
使用这种高效的结果
reactive Gateway project alright so with
反应性网关项目还可以
that we've looked at just a number of
我们只看了一些
different technologies in the spring
Spring 不同的技术
ecosystem we've looked at a you know the
我们研究过的生态系统
these the seeding of a new project using
这些是使用新项目的种子
the call and all open plugin and the
通话和所有打开的插件以及
spring initializer and the complan
Spring初始值设定项和Complan
support there we looked at how to use
支持那里，我们研究了如何使用
functional beam definitions we looked at
我们看过的功能光束定义
integration with Kotlin community
与Kotlin社区整合
technologies like exposed and looked at
像暴露和观察的技术
how to you know integrate that with
您如何知道与
spring apparatus like the platform
平台式Spring 装置
transaction manager we looked at using
我们使用的交易管理器
spring MVC style controllers and then we
Spring MVC样式控制器，然后我们
looked at how to do you know how to use
看了怎么知道你怎么用
the reactive support in Spring Framework
Spring Framework中的反应式支持
5 and spring butoh
5和 Spring butoh
for functional reactive endpoints here
此处用于功能性反应性端点
we did that with the function reactive
我们通过反应功能做到了这一点
endpoints there and then we also looked
那里的端点，然后我们也看了看
at sprinkler gateway and its DSL so at
在喷水网关及其DSL上
this point you know this doesn't look
这一点你知道这看起来不
anything like you've probably seen
像你可能看到的任何东西
before functional beam definitions Plus
在功能束定义之前
this DSL this is all spring this results
这个DSL，这是整个 Spring 的结果
in an object that gets managed by the
在由...管理的对象中
application context right same thing for
应用程序上下文对同样的事情
this this gives me this results in an
这给了我这个结果
object that gets managed by the
由管理的对象
application context all of that is done
应用程序上下文全部完成
for you and you don't have to worry
为你，你不必担心
about you know figuring that out but it
关于你知道搞清楚，但是
is just objects these are just objects
只是对象，这些只是对象
you can pick them apart and replace
您可以将它们拆开并更换
parts of them and so on you get all the
他们的一部分，等等，你得到了所有
full minutes of that while getting a
一整分钟的时间
much more clean concise sort of approach
更简洁的方法
to to building applications and I can
来构建应用程序，我可以
see why for example the the folks at on
看看为什么例如
the Gradle team have also supported
Gradle团队也支持
Kotlin as a language for building great
Kotlin是建立伟大的语言
alright Gradle is a very clean concise
好了Gradle非常简洁
DSL for building build files for
用于构建构建文件的DSL
describing build files and there's a
描述构建文件，有一个
nice typesafe DSL they're using Kotlin I
他们正在使用Kotlin I的不错的Typesafe DSL
expect of course that one day
当然希望有一天
you'll be able to go to start to uh
您将可以开始
spring that IO and choose Kotlin and
IO，然后选择Kotlin和
you'll get a build.gradle file with
您将获得一个build.gradle文件
Kotlin instead of just goofy I'm hoping
Kotlin不仅仅是愚蠢的我希望
that's what's gonna happen one day as
那就是一天会发生的事情
well so right now we've just got maven
好吧，现在我们才有了Maven
in Gradle but imagine if you had Gradle
在Gradle中，但想像一下您是否拥有Gradle
with common in addition of course to the
除了常见的
wonderful groovy language alright so
好极了的时髦语言
with that my friend thanks so much for
和我的朋友非常感谢
watching and we'll see you next time
看，下次见
you
您